You!
You're the man who's always in my dreams.
You're telling me something.
Protect my daughter.
You might be going against
someone influential.
And I don't want my daughter to get involved.
I know that Sep's life was short.
But many people love him.
What do you mean by short life?
- I don't understand you.
- Liam, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Tell me, what's happening? Where's Sep?
Sep is dead.
That night, we heard him screaming.
When we went out,
we saw him on the ground unconscious.
When we went to the gate,
it smelled like gasoline around the area.
This office needs a new monster.
- I'm your man.
- Make sure of it, Vergil.
Because I'm not the type of man
who patiently waits to get what he wants.
I don't get why Joyce
is making me fix her wedding.
I might take care of their honeymoon, too.
I'm sure Hans will be glad. Right, Hans?
What's keeping you busy these days?
To be fair to Joyce,
she's also busy with the medical mission
and renovation project
of the orphanage, right?
Do we have vloggers and reporters there?
It's a waste
if there's no media coverage
to show my daughter's saintly deeds.
Right?
Anyway, let us proceed.
I will show you the plan, okay?
The theme... is water goddess realness.
There will be overflowing water
in the vases outside the church.
And there will be singing divas.
Five of them!
Singing like mermaids.
They will sing at the wedding.
And you know, it's going to be...
Too much!
Babe, did you approve this?
I want it to be simple.
I told you that, right?
Babe...
Auntie's suggestion is fine.
At least, our relationship has
been low-key before, right?
Now, for once, I just want the whole world...
And the universe, rather...
To know you're mine.
The universe, as Auntie said.
Sir Hans, excuse me.
Madam, I somehow agree with Miss Joyce.
Isn't it too showy?
It might take away
the solemnity of the ceremony.
Why didn't you go to the meeting
if that's what you want?
Why didn't you sit down with them?
I've settled everything already,
and now you want to change the plan.
I'm busy too.
And you, Odet...
if you want to take Joyce's side,
you better walk her down the aisle too!
Mommy, honestly, I'm just overwhelmed with...
Babe, where?
Expenses?
Budget?
Babe...
I told you, I saved up for this
for a long time.
This is for us. We deserve this.
Babe.
It's going to be
the wedding of the century!
Imagine.
A big star will marry a hotshot lawyer
who is also a promising politician.
They really are a power couple!
Powerful, powerful!
What can you say, babe?
If that's what you want,
then I'm okay with it.
Perfect!
So now, I will show you...
the gown with a super long train.
Let's eat, love.
Don't you want the food?
I can order pizza.
No need. I'm okay with that.
How's your project with Joyce
at the orphanage?
You're lucky she has time for that...
despite her busy schedule.
We are doing okay.
There is a lot to repair in the orphanage.
The kids' living condition could be better.
Love, do you want me to fix your schedule?
I notice that you seem to...
forget your promise to my father.
Didn't you say you'll help in his campaign?
Via...
Didn't I tell you
that I'm having second thoughts
about that project?
But you're not having second thoughts
about me, right?
Laugh a little!
I'm joking.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Dad's busy, too, with Casa Fuerte.
I thought Congressman Ramon
had already let go of Casa Fuerte?
He only let go of Uncle Danilo, remember?
He's still hands-on
with your brother, Vergil.
You know what, love?
You should hang out with him more
instead of your showbiz friends.
You will learn a lot from him.
Maybe you're right.
There's a lot I need to learn.
I'm glad you came.
It's only now that I enjoy my time
since I retired from work.
Dad...
The truth is, I came here because...
I want to know something about Casa Fuerte.
You don't need to know anything
about Casa Fuerte.
Business as usual.
And I don't work there anymore.
If you want to know something...
you can ask Vergil.
He's on his way here.
How can we be sure that
he'll tell me the truth?
You know my brother.
He's so...
So...
Intelligent?
Great?
I didn't know you admired me, Liam.
You know what?
I asked you to come here
to join me in my quiet time.
But I think I made a mistake
inviting you both.
Can we just have coffee?
What does he want to know?
What are your new projects in Casa Fuerte?
Why? Do you want to apply?
Try talking to HR.
What are your projects with Uncle Ramon?
Why would I tell you?
Now that I'm the CEO,
you can't order me around anymore.
Also, you might end up getting jealous.
An airport in the south.
A big mall up north.
And an old orphanage that will
become a condominium.
You're surprised, right?
What orphanage are you referring to?
Ask Uncle Ramon about it.
What?
Are you scared to ask him?
Because of all the wrong things
you did to his family?
Tell me, Liam.
Are you still cheating on Via?
- Vergil, stop.
- Don't change the topic.
Bahay Aruga.
Uncle Ramon wants that property.
There you go.
I said it.
You can now leave.
Go wherever the hell you want
to do soul searching.
I know you and Uncle Ramon.
I know you'll try everything
just to get that property.
Now, tell me.
A kid died there.
Do you have something to do with it?
We heard him screaming that night.
He sounded like he was fighting with someone.
And when we went out,
we saw him on the ground, unconscious.
Do you know what's puzzling?
When we went to the gate,
the whole place smelled like gasoline.
Liam, what are you talking about?
What? Answer me.
Dad...
are you just going to let your bastard child
disrespect me?
Don't forget, I now have the highest position
in the company.
Please!
Stop, both of you!
You, Liam.
Be careful with your words.
And you, Vergil.
I want to know everything!
All your dealings with Ramon.
Ask your friend, then.
[Medical Mission]
Aren't you needed in your filming?
We might be taking up too much of your time.
Sister...
I'm available any time for you.
Thank you.
You're early.
I need to ask Sister something.
What is it, son?
Sister...
Is anyone interested in this land
where the orphanage is standing?
How did you know?
They're too pushy.
I'm close to reporting them to the police.
Is that Casa Fuerte?
Yes, they insist on buying this land.
I turned them down several times.
But they're so persistent.
What will happen to the kids? Poor kids.
I will never forget that name. Casa Fuerte.
Sorry, Liam, I realized only now
that you're a Herrera.
You own Casa Fuerte.
Maybe you can ask your company
to stop trying to buy this land.
I feel bad for the kids.
Don't worry, Sister.
Even though I'm no longer
part of Casa Fuerte,
I will do everything I can
to prevent them from buying this property.
Thank you.
Now I'm hopeful that someone can help us.
Excuse me.
Sister, there's a call for you.
Is that so?
I'll leave you for now. I'll be right back.
Liam...
Why is Casa Fuerte
interested in the orphanage?
Actually, I just talked with Vergil.
Honestly, I don't know
what Congressman Ramon's plans are.
It's Congressman Ramon dela Peña again?
What does he plan to do with this orphanage?
We're late. They might get mad.
Oh! Wait, baby.
Hello!
Sorry. Sorry, Sir.
Sorry, I'm late. I had to pick up Astig first.
Hello, Astig.
I've been wanting to meet you.
Hello.
Sorry. I can't leave him with his dad.
We had a fight last night.
He didn't give financial support again.
It's okay, Megan.
It's okay.
Are you sure, Sir?
Looks like you're having a serious talk.
My God. Here we go again.
I thought we already hit rock bottom
when we stayed in the movie
just so you can be with Liam.
I didn't know it could get worse.
- This is desperation...
- Sister, these are vitamins.
You can give it to the kids.
There's vitamin C...
- An orphanage?
- To prevent them from viruses.
Love!
Hi.
I brought some clothes.
My celebrity and model friends
heard about your project for the orphans.
So they sent some clothes.
There, perfect. Hey, Odet.
Instead of just standing there,
why don't you help me instead.
Odet!
Excuse me?
I have a role to play here.
How about you? What's your part?
Just because you are
wearing heavier makeup
doesn't make you better than me.
We're both assistants.
And with your arms,
you can definitely handle that job!
And you have hideous feet.
Keep away those eyesores!
- What?
- At least it's just my feet.
You look hideous all over!
Hey!
Ma'am, stop me.
Girl, let's go.
Are you going somewhere, Joyce?
Are you leaving because I came?
It's not like that, Via.
I need to take care of something.
I have to meet Hans.
Liam, is it okay if I go ahead?
I told Megan everything
that needs to be done.
Love?
Joyce is asking if she can leave.
Yes.
Be safe.
Sorry, Via.
I have a prior commitment.
Don't be sorry.
We really should value our commitments.
Bye.
Don't tell me I can't stay here, too.
This is for the kids.
Give Sister the clothes.
Sister?
Here are branded clothes for the kids.
Those with broken hearts
can also use it to wipe their tears.
Chef, thank you so much for your time.
I'm glad Hans tapped you for our wedding.
I can't say no to Hans.
And I'm super honored
that you picked me for your special day.
I don't often cook for celebrities like you.
Oh, come on, Chef.
You're a celebrity, too.
- That's right.
- You're more famous, Joyce.
I bumped into you on the set
of a morning show.
I wanted to take a picture with you,
but I felt shy.
You don't have to be shy now, Chef.
You can ask my wife
to make video greetings.
You can ask for three or four.
That's embarrassing, babe.
I'd love that, bro.
Actually, my friends are
big fans of all your hit movies.
And because of that,
I'll be preparing my go-to
and favorite dishes
for your wedding reception.
- It will be a blockbuster too.
- That's a blockbuster.
And here's my menu proposal.
Let's see.
Wait. Comfort food?
Isn't this too fatty, Chef?
Not necessarily for the super healthy people.
But my menu will really indulge you.
It will be so delicious,
and I promise you, guys,
it won't let you down.
You said so yourself.
Just once.
Wait. Don't we have other choices?
Can we talk about it first?
Sure, Mr. and Mrs. Arevalo.
I'll leave you for now.
But I'll ask for a video greeting later.
Babe?
Don't you think Aunt Joanne will get mad
if we have that at our wedding?
You and my mom
almost decided on everything
regarding our wedding.
Is it okay if I decide on the food?
Babe, sorry, but...
I'm just thinking about your endorsements...
Especially the organic food space.
Don't you think it's too...
This menu, it's a bit out of your...
Why do you talk like my mom?
Babe, I'm just concerned about
your image as a celebrity.
Hans, I'm the one you're going to marry,
not my image.
Miss Via, thank you for the clothes.
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Anytime, Sister. You're welcome.
Excuse me, Sister.
Excuse me, Sir.
What are you doing here?
Uncle Ramon told me to come here.
Our future Senator.
So it's true that you're having
the orphanage renovated.
Keep the orphanage out of your dirty job.
So this is why you don't have time
for Uncle Ramon's campaign.
You're wasting your time on this nonsense.
I'm glad you're the ones here,
and not the other woman...
Vergil.
- Hey, Hans!
- Judge Policarpio.
Good day. This is Joyce.
I'm glad I saw you.
I couldn't contact you.
Perfect timing, you're with Joyce.
Hello.
I'm Reggie Policarpio.
Yes, Judge. I know you.
I just want to ask you about my movie offer.
I want to produce a movie.
And I told Hans about it.
This is about one of the cases I handled.
It's about an abused mom
who fought for her kids' custody.
The story is very inspiring.
Hans? Looks like you haven't told Joyce yet.
Sorry, Judge.
I forgot about it.
We're busy taking care of our wedding.
No worries. I understand.
Sorry, I forgot you're getting married.
Maybe we're just going
to get another actress.
We can hear your pitch, Judge.
I will have my mom talk to you.
Sure. With Ma'am Joanne?
Thanks for considering.
We can really see you for the role.
We'll wait for your call.
Thank you so much.
Be safe, Judge.
I'll go ahead.
Did you forget to tell me?
Or you purposely tried to block
a potential project?
Sorry, Joyce.
For seven years,
I've been sharing you with the world.
I just thought...
maybe there's a chance
I could have you only for myself.
Hans, this is me, and this is what I do.
You loved me as I am.
Joyce, no.
You know how big a deal it is for me
when people control my life.
You know that.
No. It's not that...
What if we're already married?
What other decisions will you make
without me knowing?
Joyce, it's not...
Joyce.
I won't waste your time, Sister.
Looks like you're busy
and will probably do your novena later.
How much money are we talking about here?
Name your price.
This will be a big help for the kids.
The Congressman can pay
for what you need.
I thought...
you understood that we're not interested
in selling this land.
If the land is your concern,
we have lots of it.
More spacious and way better.
We have lands overlooking the city.
We have properties near the beach.
Sister, kids love the beach.
I know why you're Interested in this land.
What will the kids say
if they learn they were kicked out
because you want to convert their house
into a gambling den?
Forgive me. I'm sorry, son.
I disagree with your plan.
Sorry, Sir.
But I have a background in Psychology.
We take care of kids
who experienced severe trauma.
It's not good for them
if we move them to another place.
Vergil...
Can you stop being a puppet
to grow dirty money?
We were given a chance to change.
But what did you choose?
You chose to be greedy.
I dreamt of something.
It's like an alternate reality.
And in that dream...
I saw how you rot in jail.
Don't test my patience, Liam!
If you try to bring me down,
I will take you with me.
I don't care if Dad gets involved.
- We'll all end up in jail.
- Keep Dad out of this.
I'm warning you.
You're playing the good son again, huh?
Go and be with Dad!
You're both like dogs
whose tails have been cut off.
That's enough.
Stop. That's enough.
Please stop. I'm begging you.
That's enough.
Stop threatening us.
We're having a medical mission
because a kid died of sickness.
His name is Sep.
The kids are just starting to recover
and be hopeful that they won't
end up like Sep,
who died because we had no money
for his medication.
Sister, I'm sorry.
It looks like my brother already
sold his soul to the devil.
Oh, really?
- Stop!
- Hey!
Come on!
Stop it!
Go ahead!
- Go and try to do something! You!
- Don't!
- Stop!
- You! Move there!
Please stop. My God. Merciful heaven.
Please stop.
Try me, Liam!
I didn't want to use violence.
But you're testing my patience!
You, Liam.
You know what happens to those
who get in the way
of the Congressman's plans.
Does Papa know about that, Vergil?
Stop making a scene here!
We know we're just ordinary people.
We're not at your level.
But please don't harass us.
Please think of the children's welfare.
Just because you'll give money
and offer another land
doesn't mean the kids will accept it.
Our life is simple. But we are happy.
Please, leave us alone.
Vergil Herrera!
Stop what you're doing.
Do you do that to scare people?
Why don't you try me?
Let's see what happens
to the congressman you idolize
once I speak up about what you did here.
We're not done yet.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Do you have ice?
Sister... are you okay?
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Joyce, I'm sorry about earlier.
I just had a hard time trying to...
to have control.
Isn't that how life is?
We don't have control over everything.
Maybe we really are alike.
As for me...
I have so many "what ifs".
What is Liam Herrera's...
"what if"?
What if...
I did not make
the big mistake I did before...
in my attempt to make everything right?
I did not know that...
I would lose the people who love me.
How about you?
What are your "what ifs"?
What if...
I dared to take a risk?
What if Sep is still with us?
What if there is a way to change the past?
Let's go.
Sister might already be looking for us.
Joyce...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Joyce.
Liam, we just talked about wrong decisions.
Let's choose what's right.
Hello, friends!
[Girl With Periwinkle Hair]
It's me again,
your trusted showbiz authority.
The Girl with the Periwinkle Hair!
I'm not sure what kind of love boat
Joycelyn Trinidad is in.
Some of you might say that I have no basis.
Well, see it for yourselves.
Do you know how it will affect my campaign?
Now, I have to act,
so they won't call me a bad father.
I have warned you a long time ago
about those snakes.
Then don't, Dad.
Don't protect me...
if you're only worried about
your campaign as a senator.
Haven't you thought about it?
Your only child has been
cheated on by her boyfriend!
Via.
Via!
Come back here!
We can deny it.
We can say that it's just
someone who looks like Joyce.
Right?
Or there's someone who wants to ruin her.
- Right?
- We can use that.
Or say that the picture was edited.
Let's release edited photos.
Or let's make it look like
it's taken from a bad angle.
- Yes.
- Liam could just be
whispering something to her.
But the angle made it
look like they were kissing.
- We can do that, right?
- Let's try it.
- Perfect.
- Odet, take a picture of us.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
Can we please... not worry about it for now?
Everyone's talking about
our daughter's private life.
There are many speculations
and judgments about her.
And what do you want to do?
You want to make it look like it's fake news?
Dad, let them be.
You should really let us be.
Because no one cleans up your mess but me.
And now you're going to tolerate her?
There would have been nothing to clean up
if only your daughter
didn't flirt with another guy.
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Liam, we don't want to interfere
with whatever relationship
you and Joyce have.
- But...
- But,
Miss Joyce is a famous celebrity.
The orphanage is getting
dragged into the issue.
They say that we're covering up
your affair...
That we're tolerating you...
And that you turned the orphanage
into your rendezvous.
The medical mission you organized
for the kids is a really big help.
But we're also facing
a serious issue right now.
I understand, Lerna.
Sister...
Arnel.
What's going on between you and Liam?
We were just talking.
We became emotional.
Was it about our fight the other day?
Joyce?
Don't you like me anymore?
Nothing's going on between Liam and me.
See? You're not answering my question.
I'm asking you if you don't like me anymore.
Hans...
I've waited for you for seven years.
Seven years.
And then suddenly...
that.
You've known Liam for a short while,
but it seems like...
you've known each other better than we do.
That's how I feel, Joyce. Want to know why?
Whenever I look at you...
Whenever I see the way you look at him...
Whenever you're together,
I see how happy you are.
I know, Joyce.
I know because
you used to look at me that way.
That's enough.
Auntie, where did I go wrong?
Via...
That's enough, my dear.
That's enough.
Son, you two should talk.
Talk to Via.
Liam, let's make this work.
Maybe it's good that this happened...
So I will stop wondering
what's wrong with us.
And that's Joyce.
Love...
Love, we can still solve this.
Via, what are you saying?
How do we solve this?
Please, choose me.
Please.
Love, please?
Choose me.
Via, I'm sorry.
No.
Why are you sorry?
Because you love somebody else?
Because you cannot choose me?
Love...
Are you really going to throw away
the seven years we had?
For that bitch!
Please, please, please.
Don't do this, please.
- Here I am. This is me.
- Via, Via.
- Via...
- It's me.
Via, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too, Liam.
I don't know what can happen
because of your decision.
Via!
Via...
Via, please.
Don't do anything stupid.
Via...
I'm the reason. I'm the reason Joyce died.
Please, forgive me. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey!
You're the one I love.
Really, Love?
Yes, Love.
Joyce, thousands of fans are watching.
What do you want to tell them?
I want to say sorry...
to those who got disappointed.
I want to apologize to the people
who got affected by what I did.
Because of what happened,
I realized that it's so hard to live
under the watchful eyes of everyone.
I realized it's hard to live having to...
explain everything I do
because of malicious news.
So now, I have come to a decision.
I'll take a break from showbiz.
Cut!
What do you mean by "taking a break"?
What?
We're here for an interview.
Not to say goodbye.
Joanne, just leave Joyce be.
Joyce deserves a break
to find her peace of mind, madam.
I never asked for your stupid opinions!
Who made Joyce's career?
Who gave up her whole life for your career?
Mom, you can't talk to
Dad and Odet like that!
If you're mad, take it out on me.
There.
I took it out on you.
Now... proceed with your explanation.
And stop with your drama.
Continue.
- Sit down.
- Mom, I don't want this anymore.
How often do I have to say it?
I'm done with it.
I want to rest, Mom.
I want to breathe.
I want to get lost.
I want to get lost and find myself.
You want to get lost?
Fine! Get lost!
- Mommy!
- That's enough!
Mom...
- Madam!
- Joanne!
- What's happening?
As you climb to the top,
it devours you more and more.
It makes you more greedy.
And whenever you use the typewriter,
there's always a price to pay.
Your child with Joyce
disappears from this world.
Isn't he having a heart attack?
I'm begging...
You should have stayed out of this, kid.
All your visions are real.